(engine rumbling)
(air whooshing)
(faint country music)
♪ In a parade of losers ♪
(glass breaking)
(upbeat music)
♪ I'm just a bachelor ♪
♪ Looking for a partner ♪
♪ Someone who knows how to ride ♪
♪ Without even falling off ♪
♪ Gotta be compatible ♪
♪ Takes me to my limits ♪
♪ Girl, when I break you off ♪
♪ I promise that you won't wanna get off ♪
♪ If you're horny, let's do it ♪
♪ Ride it, my pony ♪
♪ My saddle's waiting ♪
♪ Come and jump on it ♪
♪ If you're horny, let's do it ♪
♪ Ride it, my pony ♪
♪ My saddle's waiting ♪
♪ Come and jump on it ♪
♪ Sitting here flossing ♪
♪ Peepin' your steelo ♪
♪ Just once if I had the chance ♪
♪ The things I would do to you ♪
♪ You and your body ♪
♪ Every single portion ♪
♪ Send chills up and down your spine ♪
♪ Juices flowing down your thigh ♪
♪ If you're horny, let's do it ♪
♪ Ride it, my pony ♪
♪ My saddle's waiting ♪
♪ Come and jump on it ♪
♪ If you're horny, let's do it ♪
♪ Ride it, my pony ♪
♪ My saddle's waiting ♪
♪ Come and jump on it ♪
(upbeat music)
♪ If we're gonna get nasty, baby ♪
♪ First we'll show and tell ♪
♪ 'Til I reach your ponytail ♪
♪ Look all over and through you, baby ♪
♪ Until we reach the stream ♪
♪ You'll be on my jockey team ♪
♪ If you're horny, let's do it ♪
♪ Ride it, my pony ♪
♪ My saddle's waiting ♪
♪ Come and jump on it ♪
♪ If you're horny, let's do it ♪
♪ Ride it, my pony ♪
♪ My saddle's waiting ♪
♪ Come and jump on it ♪
♪ If you're horny, let's do it ♪
♪ Ride it, my pony ♪
♪ My saddle's waiting ♪
♪ Come and jump on it ♪
♪ If you're horny, let's do it ♪
♪ Ride it, my pony ♪
♪ My saddle's waiting ♪
♪ Come and jump on it ♪
♪ If you're horny, let's do it ♪
♪ Ride it, my pony ♪
♪ My saddle's waiting ♪
♪ Come and jump on it ♪
♪ Ride it ♪